[
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "Inline elements are normally displayed without starting a new line",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 533,
        "question": "In HTML document the tags",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Should be written in upper case",
            "answer_b": "can be written in both uppercase or lowercase",
            "answer_c": "should be written in propercase",
            "answer_d": "should be written in lower case",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "Which HTML element is used to specify a header for a document or section?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "<top>",
            "answer_b": "<header>",
            "answer_c": "<head>",
            "answer_d": "<section>",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 505,
        "question": "Which of the following is an attribute of the <table> tag?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "SRC",
            "answer_b": "BOLD",
            "answer_c": "CELLPADDING",
            "answer_d": "LINK",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 497,
        "question": "Which of the following attribute is used to group elements?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "item",
            "answer_b": "itemgroup",
            "answer_c": "itemcheck",
            "answer_d": "itemprop",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "Which HTML element defines the title of a document?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "<title>",
            "answer_b": "<head>",
            "answer_c": "<meta>",
            "answer_d": "<start>",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 443,
        "question": "What is the HTML Tag for the largest heading",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "<h6>",
            "answer_b": "<head>",
            "answer_c": "<h1>",
            "answer_d": "<heading>",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 488,
        "question": "HTML Uses",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Fixed Tags Defined By The Language",
            "answer_b": "Pre-specified Tags",
            "answer_c": "Tags Only For Linking",
            "answer_d": "User Defined Tags",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "Which HTML element is used to specify a footer for a document or section?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "<footer>",
            "answer_b": "<section>",
            "answer_c": "<bottom>",
            "answer_d": "<down>",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 531,
        "question": "To create a blank line in your web page",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "press Enter two times",
            "answer_b": ". insert <BLINE>",
            "answer_c": "insert <BR> tag",
            "answer_d": "press Shift + Enter",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "correct_answer": "answer_a",
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "HTML"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Code",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    }
]
